[theme music playing]
[ominous music playing]
[Emilia] He can't come back yet.
I don't want to be his slave.
I understand you, Emilia.
I don't want you
to go through the same thing
my sister did with Julio.
[Emilia] Senator Pablo spoke to me.
[in English] And it's final,
I'm running for Senate.
[Ivy] I have to stop Emilia.
I can't let her run for senator,
because if she wins,
she'll have the power to manipulate
our judicial system.
[Jepoy] Arthur's recovering safely.
We already have Tonio too.
But I need more whistleblowers
against Emilia.
Butchoy has a love letter for you.
-[Ivy] Butchoy is so cute.
-Um…
I guess I've got more competition now.
[Ivy] You know,
love is just a distraction
from important things.
[in English] I want you
to support Arnaldo.
[Ivy in English] Arnaldo and Emilia.
You want to pit the son
against his mother?
[in English] Competitions like this
produce good results.
[in English] Ms. Aguas,
I was born to lead.
And this is my chance.
I'd rather support Emilia
than you.
[in English] What can I do
to change your mind?
The farmers' land.
Are you doing this
for the farmers or for Diego?
[Ivy] It's not my fault if your brother
moves faster than you do.
[Emilia in English] The support
you promised
for my father's candidacy.
Where's the money? Give it to me.
I said I'd support your father, not you.
What newspaper is that?
[Belen] It has a picture of a woman.
Her name is Ivy Aguas.
She's really interested in it.
She keeps looking at it.
Who were you talking to, Raul?
[tense music playing]
It was just my aunt.
Really?
I thought it was the mistress
Emilia was telling me about.
She told me to keep an eye on you.
You know, Auntie,
I think it'd be better if…
you stayed out of our problems.
[scoffs]
Raul…
I don't plan on arguing with you.
[in English] The truth is,
I want you and Emilia to sort things out.
For this family,
and for my niece's reputation.
You owe her everything, Raul.
[in English] You won't have anything
if not for her.
[in English] So, if I were you,
Don't wait for her to lose
whatever love she feels for you.
Well, I'm not scared of Emilia.
And just so you know,
our relationship's been dead
for a long time now.
[tense music playing]
Hey, girl.
Do you know what happened
to your favorite client?
Of course.
Yesterday, she confronted
her husband's mistress,
[in English] who, by the way,
was his business partner!
Unbelievable.
Snakes these days act like rats.
They'll dig into any holes
just to get what they want.
Exactly.
[in English] I shouldn't have left Arnaldo
with that girl, Ivy.
Ouch!
[in English] Can you watch
what you're doing?
-[in English] I'm sorry, ma'am.
-Sorry?
[in English] I can get you fired,
you know?
Forget it.
[ominous music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
Raul?
[in English] What's that?
Um…
[tense music playing]
Ivy, again?
-What's your problem, Emilia?
-You!
Everyone in this house is my problem!
[in English] You're all
keeping secrets from me!
What?
How can I keep a secret
when you're keeping me
locked up in this house?
And I will keep you locked here
until you dump your mistress.
What are you talking about?
I don't have any mistresses.
Stop this, Emilia.
Okay, Raul.
If it's true you don't have
any other women…
then kneel before me.
Kiss my feet, and say you love me.
[tense music playing]
See?
[in English] You're lying!
[in English] You're lying again!
Why do I even put up with this?
[in English] Please…
Don't give me anymore reasons.
[in English] Don't push me.
[in English] Piece of advice,
Raul, from your wife.
If you're getting bored
just staying in this house…
then you should just serve me.
[Natalie] Hi, Auntie!
-Natalie.
-Uh…
[in English] I'm so sorry to barge in.
[in English] I've been looking
for Arnaldo.
Is he here?
[in English] I checked in his office
and he wasn't there.
[in English] And last I checked.
He was with Ivy.
[in English] Natalie, tell me.
[in English] Is he being considered
by the party to run for Senate?
Um…
[in English] Yes, he is.
[in English] I thought you already knew.
[tense music playing]
-[suspenseful music playing]
-[man grunts]
[cocks gun]
-Tonio.
-No! No!
Please don't!
Out!
You need to calm down a little, dude.
Here, cool down.
Your happy days are over, Tonio.
It's time for you to talk.
Take it easy.
Just let me get out of here for a while.
And I swear I'll tell you
everything I know.
Bastard!
Go ahead!
Put it down.
I'm already fed up with you.
What if I torture you
until you croak like a frog?
[tense music playing]
[in English] Is this from your
personal account, Ms. Ivy?
[in English] Yes.
I'm buying that property
for personal reasons.
Good thing it's still up
for public auction.
Apparently, the family who owned
this property are all dead.
Joan, as soon as you get the deed of sale,
secure the property immediately.
[in English] Yes, Ms. Aguas.
I will.
Ivy, the mayor's here.
-[in English] We're fine, Nanny.
-Thank you.
[in English] Ms. Aguas.
[clears throat] Mr. Mayor.
[pensive music playing]
[in English] I'm a man of my word,
Ms. Aguas.
TRANSFER CERTIFICATE OF TITLE
IVY AGUAS, OF LEGAL AGE, FILIPINO
I hope you are too.
I can see you really want
to win your prize.
Well, not just that.
I want you to support my senate bid…
Instead of my mom's.
[in English] That's why
I brought this with me.
[in English] Stated there is the support
I need from you,
[in English] starting from the campaign,
[in English] up to the moment
of my proclamation.
[in English] Mr. Mayor…
One at a time.
[sensual music playing]
Diego, why are you here?
Um, is Ivy home?
She's inside, talking to the mayor.
Do you want to come in?
[sensual music continues playing]
[in English] You forget that I'm a hunter,
Ms. Aguas.
[in English] I'm not satisfied
with just one catch.
[in English] Mr. Mayor.
Why can't you just let me?
-[Carlotta] Uh…
-It's all right.
I'll be going now. Excuse me. Thanks.
-[in English] Excuse me.
-Yes?
-[in English] Is Arnaldo here?
-Uh…
-Wait, he's…
-[Natalie] Arnaldo!
-[Carlotta] Oh!
-Arnaldo!
[Natalie in English] You're such a bitch,
aren't you?
You just won't stop flirting
with my boyfriend, will you?
-Well?
-Natalie.
-[Arnaldo] Natalie.
-You're such a flirt!
-You bitch!
-Natalie!
[tense music playing]
[Natalie screaming, gasping]
[tense music continues playing]
[whimpering]
[Arnaldo in English] Come here.
[Arnaldo in English] Give me your hand.
[in English] Come on. Come here.
-Don't touch me!
-Natalie.
-What's wrong with you?
[in English] I'm warning you.
Stay away from my boyfriend.
We aren't doing anything.
[in English] Liar!
Enough! What's wrong with you?
I came here to give her
the title of the farmers' land.
[in English] To convince her to support
my senatorial bid!
You shouldn't argue with her!
[in English] I don't care.
[in English] I don't care!
[in English] From now on.
[in English] I forbid you
to see this woman.
[in English] Or else I'm going
to tell my dad.
Choose.
Ivy,
[in English] or my daddy's support
for your senatorial ambition.
-Natalie…
-Choose!
[tense music playing]
[exasperated sigh]
Natalie.
Let's talk. Natalie!
That Natalie is so scary.
It's a good thing Diego was here.
-I'm fine, Nanny.
-[sighs]
Thank you, Diego.
It's nothing.
Wait, why are you here?
["Sa'Yo" instrumental playing]
I just wanted to give you this.
I have to do something inside.
I'll leave you two there.
Do you remember those flowers?
They're the same ones I gave you
when I first saw you after the contest.
Thank you.
About what Arnaldo said earlier…
about the farmers' land…
Was that true?
Ivy, why are you doing this?
[Ivy sighs]
They are the rightful owners of that land.
It was donated to them long ago.
I just want to do the right thing
and give them back what's theirs.
Ivy, thank you.
Thank you so much!
[in English] Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I just got carried away.
The farmers will be thrilled
when they hear about this!
Thank you.
["Sa'Yo" instrumental continues playing]
[Arnaldo] Natalie!
-Natalie, come on. Let's talk.
-Stop it, Arnaldo!
You don't need to tell the senator on me.
Calm down!
[in English] Stop talking to me!
[in English] And go to hell.
[in English] I'm sorry, okay? I'm sorry.
It's a good thing your mom
told me where you were.
You know what you deserve?
You need to be taught a lesson.
[in English] That's why I'm telling
my dad to remove you
[in English] from the senatorial list,
so you'll learn
you can't have everything you want!
-[in English] Natalie, come on.
-[screams] Don't touch me!
[in English] Go!
[in English] Just go.
[in English] I hate you!
[heavy breathing]
[whimpering]
[Arnaldo] Mom!
Why did you let Natalie go see Ivy?
She was looking for you.
[in English] I thought you'd be with Ivy.
[in English] Don't play dumb with me.
I know you did it on purpose.
You knew I'd go to Ivy
and ask for her endorsement
to replace Grandpa.
[in English] Now that Natalie's mad at me,
[in English] her father's also mad at me!
[in English] There goes my chance
against you.
[clapping furiously]
[in English] Well played! I didn't think
you could be so selfish!
[in English] How dare you talk
to me that way?
You're the one who's selfish.
You think I don't know
you gave the farmers' land title to Ivy?
So, what?
I have every right to use that
because it's under my name!
[in English] I have every right
to use that
to help me with my political ambitions!
Why are you so selfish?
Have you forgotten that we're a family?
We should help each other
instead of going against one another!
[tense music playing]
Arnaldo.
[in English] I know your grandfather
groomed you to follow in his footsteps.
But you're still young.
You have your future ahead of you.
You can still prove your worth.
[in English] This is my time.
[in English] This is my last chance
[in English] to prove my worth
to your grandpa.
[in English] Don't steal it from me.
[suspenseful music playing]
Arnaldo.
[in English] Please, give this to me.
[sobbing]
[sniffles]
[in English] Do you want me
to get the land title back from Ivy?
[suspenseful music continues playing]
[in English] No need. I have a plan.
[exhales]
[in English] Thank you.
[in English] You're the best son
any mother could ever ask for.
[sighs in relief]
[ominous music playing]
It's ours. This land is ours!
Everyone! Thank you very much.
We are indebted to you.
Ever since the dispersal,
you've really helped us out.
-That's right.
-Exactly.
-You're welcome, Mr. Fernan.
-Thank you, Ms. Ivy.
The truth is, it's yours.
The land is yours.
I just did what's right
and gave back the title to you.
-Thank you so much!
-Thank you!
Thank you very much.
-Thank you.
-[applauding]
Ms. Beautiful!
This is for you,
so you'll always remember
how thankful we are.
-[woman] Wow.
-[man] Nice.
[in English] Thank you, Butchoy.
Ms. Beautiful, can I have a kiss?
[everyone gasps and laughs]
Of course, you can!
[cheering and applause]
-You're so cute!
-[man] Oh, wow.
You're so cute, Butchoy.
[tender music playing]
-[man] Let's try it.
-[laughter]
-[man] The other side.
-[woman] Cat got his tongue. Look.
[laughing]
[cheering and applause]
[in English] Governor, I've set
your lunch date with Judge Rivas
[in English] and Mrs. Segovia
of the Land Registration Authority.
[in English] Good.
[in English] Can you please call up Ivy?
Tell her I have what she needs.
Will do, Madam.
[ominous music playing]
-[knocking on door]
-[door opens]
[in English] Hey.
What are these flowers for?
[in English] I don't want to talk to you.
Natalie.
[in English] Come on, please understand.
I need to do those things.
You need to flirt with her?
[in English] Arnaldo, I don't think so.
[in English] It's a political strategy.
Your father does it too.
Even so.
[in English] I thought you'd be different.
[in English] I am different.
[quiet music playing]
[in English] Prove it.
[sensual music playing]
[exhales]
[sensual music continues playing]
So, I'll get going.
I have a lot to take care of.
Thank you again. Take care, Ms. Ivy!
[townsfolk] Thank you for your help,
Ms. Ivy.
Ms. Ivy, I'm sorry,
but our car broke down.
The fan belt got snipped again.
We need to have it towed back to the shop.
-It's broken again?
-Yes.
Okay. I'll just call someone to tow it.
-Okay, ma'am.
-Can I…
-Of course!
-Sure! Please sit down.
We'll call for you!
Uh, Ivy, I'll drive you home.
If it's all right with you.
[man] Let him drive you home, ma'am.
You should let him, ma'am.
So, you're driving her home now, huh?
Oh, that depends on Butchoy.
-[man] Come on. Let her.
-Let her.
-[woman] What can you say, Butchoy?
-[man] Is it okay?
Is it okay if Diego drives me home?
Yes, Butchoy, let him drive her home.
Okay.
[upbeat music playing]
[soft music playing]
[sentimental music playing]
That's my best friend's favorite toy.
I know some places here in Ardiente…
that are really peaceful.
If you want, we can check them out.
[sentimental music continues playing]
Really?
Let's go.
[engine rumbling]
[tender music playing]
What are we doing here?
Didn't I say I'd bring you somewhere
a little more peaceful?
[birds cawing]
Come on!
[tender music continues playing]
Ivy!
This is going to be our new home!
[exhales]
[Diego] Ivy!
Come here.
This was my best friend Lily's old house.
Actually…
This was where I felt what it was like
to have a happy family.
Lily's parents accepted me for who I am.
No judgment.
Like…
Like a part of their family.
[tender music playing]
[in English] Thank you so much,
Lucy and Helen.
I know how busy you both are,
[in English] but you still entertained
my request to come here.
[in English] It's nothing, Emilia.
Compared to what you've done for me
[in English] to be the town's
provincial judge.
[both chuckle]
[in English] And for making me the head
of the Land Registration Authority.
[in English] So…
[in English] Does that mean you'll give me
the land title I asked for?
[in English] Of course, it's legal
under PD 1529.
We can already transfer
the ownership under your name.
[in English] In fact, I already gave
the court order to Helen.
I had this rushed earlier, Emilia.
Here's the new deed to the land.
[ominous music playing]
TRANSFER CERTIFICATE OF TITLE
EMILIA ARDIENTE TORILLO,
OF LEGAL AGE, FILIPINO
[instrumental theme music playing]
This over here…
used to be the day care center
of Lily's mother.
Teacher Camia.
She was the one who told me
that I could be brave.
That I could be strong.
[Ivy] Mom, what happened to you?
Hey!
Lily… Run!
Ivy.
Are you all right?
Come on, I have something else
I want to show you.
Let's go.
And…
[in English] this is where Lily
and I used to exercise.
[in English] This is where she taught me
how to do jumping jacks
[in English] and use jump ropes.
This is where she made me
run again and again
while carrying my bag.
Uh, can I borrow your bag?
-What?
-Come on, let me borrow it.
This is what she made me do.
She made me carry my bag,
and it was so heavy,
and then she would make me
run around like this.
Whoo!
[young Lily] Ready, set, go!
Hurry! Go, Diego!
Run! Come on, faster!
Just like this. I ran around in circles.
[bright music playing]
Actually, I would get so exhausted
after running just one round.
I'd be panting.
I was so fat, almost as fat as Butchoy.
My stomach was so big…
it was maybe two
or three times bigger then.
[sighs] I can't believe it.
Lily helped me so much.
[tender music playing]
Um…
You're sweating. Can I have my bag?
Oh.
You're…
You're all sweaty. Here.
Wipe it off.
Thanks.
[tender music continues playing]
It's so hot.
Lily was like my personal trainer.
You know, we used to
run circles around these trees.
Just like this.
-Whoo!
-[young Lily] Go Diego, duck!
Just one hand, no cheating!
Go! You can do it!
From here until there.
So that no matter how much I ate,
I wouldn't get fat.
Back then, I thought they were helping me
so my family would accept me.
But the truth was, they were helping me…
so I could get to know,
love, and accept myself.
Your…
Lily? Her name's Lily, right?
She's a big part of your life.
That's probably why I brought you here.
-I… Ouch!
-Oh.
-That hurts!
-Diego.
-Oh! Ouch.
[young Lily] I told you to be careful.
I'm fine.
I can't explain it.
Whenever I'm with you, Ivy…
I feel like I'm with Lily again.
[tender music playing]
Come on.
There's something else I want to show you.
-Is it all right?
-Yeah. It's fine.
It's a bit far from here.
Just watch your step.
It's a bit rocky here.
[in English] Happy?
[in English] I guess you can tell Mom
we're okay now.
[in English] As long as you promise me
that it's just me.
[in English] Just me forever.
[in English] I just don't like it
when we fight.
Me too.
[in English] It's stressful.
That's why…
you should stay away from that woman.
Because if you don't,
I'll lose my patience.
[in English] I just might kill her
with my bare hands.
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
[in English] Hello?
Okay. Tell them I'm on my way.
[ominous music playing]
[in English] I have to meet some important
people for my senatorial bid…
[in English] because whether Mom likes it
or not, I will be running for senator.
[ominous music playing]
That's what Grandpa wants,
and that's what'll happen.
[ominous music playing]
Ivy, come on!
This is it!
This is our sanctuary.
This is where we pour out
all our emotions.
All our pain, our sorrows.
You can shout out whatever you feel here.
-Lily, where are you?
-[quiet music playing]
I miss you so much!
Ivy, your turn.
Come on. Shout it out.
Lily, I hope you're happy
wherever you are!
Ivy.
Seriously, it feels so good
after you shout it out.
Come on.
[tender music playing]
[in English] Sorry.
I might be annoying you.
[in English] I just really
miss my best friend.
But I don't think she's ever coming back.
What about you?
[in English] Did you have a best friend
when you were a kid?
[tender music playing]
I was a loner.
I was always cooped up in my room.
All I did was read.
Really? I love to read too.
Just like Lily.
Do you know The Count of Monte Cristo?
[in English] "Moral wounds
have this peculiarity.
[in English] They may be hidden…
[in English] but they never close."
[in English] "Always painful,
always ready to bleed when touched…
[in English] they remain fresh
and open in the heart."
It's an amazing book.
It's about a man…
seeking revenge…
because he was abused
and imprisoned unjustly.
What about you, Diego?
Do you think what he did was right?
No.
Revenge won't get you anywhere.
But…
But what they did to him was cruel.
I understand him.
If I were him,
I'd probably do the same thing.
Uh…
I've shown you almost everything.
The next place I'm going to show you…
is the most special place
for me and my best friend.
Come on. Let's go!
Thank you for accommodating me
on such short notice.
What's this for, Mayor?
Is this about what the governor said
about you not following
in your grandpa's footsteps?
[tense music playing]
You know the governor.
She can be pretty hasty.
We're here because I want
to show you the new site
[in English] for the export
processing zone,
and to tell you that
[in English] I'll be handling
the project from now on.
That's good to hear.
No offense, Mayor, but I find
it hard to trust your mother.
I know.
That's why I want you to inform everyone
about this development,
so we can be sure
that the party chooses me.
-So, shall we?
-You can count on us, Mayor.
Ivy, come on!
This is what I was talking about.
This is the secret garden
Lily and I shared.
Beautiful, isn't it?
When she disappeared, I took care of it.
I tended the flowers,
did some landscaping…
So if she returns,
this is what she'll see.
I'm sure she'll be happy to see this.
This is her favorite place.
But, like I said…
I don't know if she's ever coming back.
I did everything, Ivy. Did you know that…
I even called out for her
on national television?
You really did that?
For Lily?
But it's been 13 years,
and I still haven't seen her.
I hope she's happy wherever she is.
But even if I don't see her again…
she'll always be my best friend.
-[tender music playing]
-[sniffles]
It's a good thing the project
will push through, Mayor.
We admire you
for standing up to your mother,
and for telling her
you're the rightful person
to run for Senate.
I just want to protect my family's name
and everything our party
has done for this town.
I'm sure your grandfather
would be proud of you.
Thanks.
Shall we begin?
I think it's best if we split up.
-[in English] All right, let's go.
-Let's go.
[instrumental theme music playing]
If…
If I were Lily…
I would probably say…
"Diego, you have to move on…
because we lead different lives now.
And I want you to be happy."
[instrumental theme music playing]
I'd say that.
If… If I were Lily.
[suspenseful music playing]
What are they doing here?
-[gunshot]
-[shrieks]
Who's that?
Don't shoot!
Oh, Diego.
It's just me.
I saw an animal, but I missed it.
Arnaldo?
[in English] Sorry, did I interrupt you?
What are you doing here?
I'm showing Ivy around.
Well, I'm showing my friends around too.
I showed them the EPZ's new location.
[in English] And, uh…
[in English] to which I wonder…
why this isn't a part
of the site's new location.
Well, it doesn't matter.
[in English] I have expansion plans,
anyway.
So, say goodbye to this place, Diego.
I have to go.
[in English] Oh, by the way,
Ms. Aguas,
don't forget, you owe me something.
[tense music playing]
No.
I won't let him have this place.
Jasmin? Do you need something?
[somber music playing]
[somber music continues playing]
[tense music plays]
Raul has to know about this.
[tender music playing]
Earlier…
I really wanted to tell him everything.
But then I thought…
what good would it do?
Nothing.
Besides, I'm sure that…
…he'll side with his family.
And…
if he finds out the truth, he'll hate me.
Ivy.
It's better this way.
Just let Lily live in his memory.
Lily is just a memory to me…
and to Diego.
Is that what you really want?
[sniffles]
[exhales]
Ivy.
Nanny, excuse me.
I still have to prepare
for my dinner with Emilia.
Ivy.
Are you sure you're ready to face Emilia?
-[in English] Natalie.
-Yay, I made it.
[in English] Hi, Auntie.
-[in English] Hi.
-Hello.
[in English] Hey, how are you and Arnaldo?
Um… We're actually really good.
That's good.
I hope you don't argue again, okay?
[in English] I know. As long as Ivy
stays out of the picture,
[in English] I guess we'll be fine.
[in English] Then you will have to
guard Arnaldo from Ivy.
[in English] I will.
[in English] That's my daughter-in-law.
Would you like to come with me?
[in English] Sure. Where are we going?
[in English] Some place where you
will witness my greatness.
[in English] I like that. Let's go?
[in English] Let's go.
[ominous music playing]
[in English] Well, I called up this
meeting to correct some mistakes.
What mistakes?
Um, Arnaldo gave you this, didn't he?
[ominous music playing]
TRANSFER CERTIFICATE OF TITLE
EMILIA ARDIENTE TORILLO
Arnaldo doesn't know that
Papa already gave that to me,
so I had it transferred under my name.
[in English] While the congressman
was in the hospital?
How did that happen? Amazing.
[in English] You know, Ivy,
when you're the governor,
[in English] you can do
everything you want.
You can raise the dead,
or make the bedridden sign papers.
[in English] Impressive, Emilia.
Now I know how the
powerful get their hands
on the land of the poor.
Ivy, I didn't steal anything.
I just made changes.
You have a point.
[in English] So,
what can I do to get this land title?
I already made a promise
to the poor farmers.
And I don't want to embarrass myself.
[in English] Oh, Ivy, another thing.
Stay away from Arnaldo.
[in English] You know that Arnaldo's
with Natalie, right?
It's not my fault.
You should talk to your son.
Since he's the one…
who keeps chasing after me.
It's getting annoying.
Ivy,
I know that Arnaldo wants you
to back him up in the Senate race.
It's true, right?
[in English] Honestly, I was hurt.
Because you kept it a secret from me.
[in English] I thought
you were loyal to me.
[in English] I am, Emilia.
[tense music playing]
That's why I'm going to buy
your overpriced property.
[in English] A hundred and fifty million.
Is that enough?
[in English] How'd you know
that's what I wanted?
Emilia… We're friends, aren't we?
We know each other really well.
Anything else?
[in English] Ivy, you know,
you're very generous.
You're such a good friend.
You give me everything I want.
[in English] But…
Let me just remind you, Emilia…
I don't like any of my friends
using me for my money.
I'm sure you know that fake people…
belong in the trash.
[in English] How dare you?
[in English] Natalie, stop.
[in English] How can you let her
talk to you like that?
[in English] [exhales]
Natalie, we're friends.
That's how the two of us talk.
[in English] We're very honest
with each other.
[in English] Yes, and Emilia and I
respect each other,
[in English] right?
[in English] Yes, and…
-[in English] we fear each other, right?
-No.
I'm not afraid of you.
[tense music playing]
Because I know
you could never hurt me, Emilia.
And that goes for me too.
[in English] Shall we eat?
[tense music continues playing]
[Pandoy clears throat]
-Auntie…
-[snorts]
I'm so happy.
[stifled laughter]
-You don't say?
-I can see that.
Why don't you try keeping
that smile of yours
from reaching the top of your head?
[laughing]
Well? Have you confessed yet?
Are you going to court her?
Uh…
Uh?
-[Loring] Eh?
-[laughing]
[ominous music playing]
[Arnaldo] I won't let Diego
steal Ivy from me.
[ominous music playing]
[panicked breathing]
Sir, please have mercy.
I'm losing my mind here!
I'm easy to talk to.
[panicked breathing]
I know you're thirsty. How about a drink?
-Yes, sir.
-Here.
Oh, it's all out.
[man] Boss, here's his food.
[Jepoy] Let him eat.
[ominous music playing]
[grunts]
[groans]
Hey. Hey!
It's okay.
He won't get far.
[Raul] That's what
I'm hoping for, Senator.
I want to resume our gambling operations.
I'm just waiting for your blessing.
I've been wanting to resume them too.
I just can't find anyone I can trust.
We go way back, right, Senator?
You can leave me in charge.
-[in English] I trust you, Raul.
-Thank you.
But after what happened--
I know I need to be extra careful.
That's what I'll do, Senator.
[in English] I hope you could
give me a chance,
and I'll be hugely indebted to you.
Okay.
Does Emilia know about this?
I don't think she needs to know.
[phone ringing]
AUNT BELEN
[in English] Excuse me, Senator.
I need to take this.
[Raul exhales]
-Hello, Auntie?
-Raul,
you need to get back here right now.
Why, Auntie? What happened to her?
I think she's coming back to her senses.
[tense music playing]
[tense music continues]
Raul, are you going somewhere?
[in English] Does Emilia know about this?
[in English] I'm sorry, I have to do this.
[in English] This is for your own good.
-[in English] Guards!
-Yes, ma'am?
Try to stop me,
and you'll get what you're asking for!
Where are you going?
[tense music playing]
You need money, right?
So, I'm gonna take care
of our gambling business.
The senator already gave me the go signal.
I don't care if the devil himself
gave you the go.
If I tell you to stay,
you're going to stay.
And I don't need money anymore…
-I have a lot of that!
-Stop it, Emilia.
If I want to leave this house,
then I will!
Raul. Raul!
Raul!
[tense music playing]
-Lily, help me.
-Mom.
Mom!
[Ivy] Jepoy, this feels different.
I want to make sure my mom really is dead.
Tomorrow's the announcement, Senator.
Are you ready to go
against your own mother?
[Raul] The higher your dreams are,
the harder you'll fall.
[in English] I am Emilia Ardiente,
[in English] destined to be a queen,
[in English] and my reign starts today.
[in English] I'm proud to present to you
the person who will complete
the senatorial line up,
[in English] a prolific leader,
none other than…
[theme music playing]